memebox.com 2016-05-07

# Privacy Policy

**Last updated: January 25th, 2014**

We reserve the right to revise and change our Privacy Policy at any time in our sole discretion, and we will post the updated version here.

Memebox cares about the information you share with us, and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This note summarizes our privacy policy. By visiting Memebox.com or any of its related applications including mobile, you are accepting the practices described in this note. 

**Why does Memebox collect personal information about customers?  **

****The information we learn from our customers helps us improve your experience with Memebox. We use your information for internal and operational purposes such as studying your preferences, delivering targeted marketing and promotional offers, and providing better and more personalized membership services including subscription. We also use the information to prevent wrongful or unauthorized uses of the website or any of its related applications. We do not sell, rent, or share your information with third party service providers, except in accordance with the purposes written above.

**What types of personal information does Memebox collect?**

  * Below are the types of information we collect:
  * _Information you give us_ : When you register with Memebox.com or make purchases, we collect the following information – your name, ID, password, email address, billing and shipping address, phone number, and payment records. You can choose not to provide certain information, but you might not be able to take advantage of some of our features including customization and communication.
  * _Automatic Information_ : We gather certain types of information when you interact with us through Memebox.com or any of its related applications to help us personalize your shopping experience and provide more rewarding services. This type of information includes IP address, referral URL, traffic to and from other sites, ad data, and standard web log information.  We may use “cookies” to obtain such information. You can find out more about our usage of “cookies” here.
  * _Information from Mobile Devices_ : When you download or use our app, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device. You may turn off location services on your device, but then you will not be able to benefit from some of our location-based services including targeted advertising, search results, and other personalization features.
  * _Information from other sources including e-mail Communications_ : We might receive information about you from other sources including your e-mail communications with us, and add it to our account information.

**How does Memebox protect your personal information?**

  * At Memebox, we value our customers’ privacy and try our best to keep your personal information secure.

**How can you access or change your personal information?**

  * You can access and change your personal information or terminate your membership at any time by signing in and clicking “Account” on the top right corner of the website. You can also change your personal information by contacting us directly. You can find the contact details at the bottom of this page. Once changes are made, we do not use previous personal information and we will also notify third party service providers of the change.

**How does Memebox use cookies?**

  * Like most other websites, we use cookies to collect information about our customers. Cookies are small data files that identify the web browser on a particular computer. When you visit Memebox.com, cookies will be sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive.Cookies help us recognize your device and provide more customized services. For instance, we use cookies to analyze the frequency and duration of visits, traffic statistics from members and non-members, customer preferences, interests in promotions, etc. The information we gather using cookies enables us to improve your shopping experience with Memebox through targeted marketing and customization features.You can choose to reject our cookies by changing your browser preferences.  If you choose to block our cookies, however, you will not be able to benefit from some of our services including personalization.

**When does Memebox share your personal information with third party service providers?**

  * We appreciate the information you share with us, and we do not sell it to others. We only disclose your personal information to third party service providers in accordance with the purposes stated above. The roles of these third party service providers include shipping, handling, and tracking packages, processing payments, managing customer information database, etc.  

**Do you have any Questions about this Privacy Policy?**

  * If you have any questions about this privacy policy or complaints regarding personal information, you can email our customer service team at: hi@memebox.com

Pre-order item. Ships once available.
